kitaab.com.pk 2019-10-07

# Privacy Policy | Kitaab

## Personal Information:-

**As You Know that Kitaab.com.pk is the web portal to provide the Educational news to its viewers and its updates on daily basis, we collect the data and provides to you. When you visit or portal or its news and in-case of any query you post a comment to our site. This information may include your name, your email address, your IP address, your ISP, the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer, Chrome, Safari or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site. Your personal information will never be released, sold, or rented to any entities or individuals outside https://www.kitaab.com.pk/**

### Cookies:-

**We also use third party advertisements on www.kitaab.com.pk to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web** **beacons when they advertise on our site. Google, through their Adsense Program, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to www.kitaab.com.pk users based on their visit to this and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy. So we are not the responsible for these cookies or data.  
**

### Third Party Companies

**Third party companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, So keep stay with the www.kitaab.com.pk (tahir@kitaab.com.pk).**

### **Further Details**

**To Get the Further Details about the Privacy Policies you must check it out here**

**We apply the strictest privacy rules in accordance to our company European collocation, here more information about GDPR requirements and rules :**  
[https://ec.europa.eu/commission/priorities/justice-and-fundamental-rights/data-protection/2018-reform-eu-data-protection-rules_en ](https://ec.europa.eu/commission/priorities/justice-and-fundamental-rights/data-protection/2018-reform-eu-data-protection-rules_en)

### **What are personal data :**

<https://ec.europa.eu/info/law/law-topic/data-protection/reform/what-personal-data_en>

### **Data processing (which apply to personal data ):**

<https://ec.europa.eu/info/law/law-topic/data-protection/reform/what-constitutes-data-processing_en>

**For more information about our use of cookies and other technologies for tracking, including how visitors can control the use of cookies, please see our** [Cookie Policy](https://automattic.com/cookies/).

**For more information on how we respond to requests for information, please see our** [Legal Guidelines](https://en.support.wordpress.com/report-blogs/legal-guidelines/).
